<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on HumLUG - Humboldt Linux Users Group</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on HumLUG - Humboldt Linux Users Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About HumLUG: The Humboldt Linux Users Group is a group of individuals in the Humboldt County area that enjoy the use of Linux and discussions about technology. We enjoy meeting and being able to spend time with interesting people who share our interests and the opportunity to learn new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/announcements/</guid>
      <description>Announcements: The website is now up to date with fully accurate meeting information for any prospective new members! The return of Thursday evening meetings! Coming soon in 2023! Official HumLUG community Matrix server! Also coming sometime in 2023 Inspirational quote of the year: &amp;ldquo;Don&amp;rsquo;t give specifc times for when things will be ready, be vague!&amp;rdquo; &amp;ndash;John</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description>HumLUG Events: Lunch meetings: HumLug meets for lunch and fun discussions about technology every friday at 12:30pm at Babe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza in Eureka.
Evening meetings: Thursday night presentations are not currently happening, but are planned to resume in 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/join/</guid>
      <description>Join HumLUG&amp;rsquo;s mailing list! If you would like to join the HumLUG mailing list then please send an email to admin@humlug.org with your request.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
