<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on HumLUG - Humboldt Linux Users Group</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on HumLUG - Humboldt Linux Users Group</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>About HumLUG: The Humboldt Linux Users Group is a group of individuals in the Humboldt County area that enjoy the use of Linux and discussions about technology. We enjoy meeting and being able to spend time with interesting people who share our interests and the opportunity to learn new things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/announcements/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/announcements/</guid>
      <description>Announcements: The return of Thursday evening presentation meetings! Second meeting: 6:00PM April 20, 2023 at the Babe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza conference room This month&amp;rsquo;s HUMLUG presentation by John will feature Internet-in-a-Box, a digital library that provides essential internet resources without an internet connection.
John will discuss the Internet-in-a-Box project and demo an installation with 700GB of offline educational resources available through a wireless hotspot. Learn how you can set up a machine with offline versions of Wikipedia, Project Gutenberg, calibre-web, Lokole email, Khan Academy, Kolibri, MediaWiki, Moodle, NextCloud, Open Street Maps, Stack Exchange, Node Red, TEDTalks, WordPress and a selection of other useful open-source offline educational resources.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/events/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/events/</guid>
      <description>HumLUG Events: Lunch meetings: HumLug meets for lunch and fun discussions about technology every friday at 11:30pm at Babe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza in Eureka.
Evening meetings: We have monthly presentation focussed meetings on the third Thursday at 6:00PM at Babe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza in Eureka.
Second meeting: 6:00PM April 20, 2023 at the Babe&amp;rsquo;s Pizza conference room Presentation by John covering Internet-in-a-Box, a digital library that provides essential internet resources without an internet connection.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/join/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/join/</guid>
      <description>Join HumLUG&amp;rsquo;s mailing list! If you would like to join the HumLUG mailing list then please send an email to admin@humlug.org with your request.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
